sogame.com 2014-08-20

# Sogame:A flow of fun

This data privacy policy informs you of which personal data is being collected by Sogame as part of our Internet services and games. It also explains how that data is processed and used. The protection of your personal information is important to us.

  **Collection of Information**

 When you use any of the Websites or Services (including through a Third Party Platform) we will collect any information you provide to us directly such as the following:

**Registration Information:** In order to use certain features of the Websites or Services, you may be required to register for an account, and in that case, we will collect and store any registration information you share with us such as, without limitation, your date of birth, age, e-mail address, password and other information that helps us confirm your access to your account and understand more about who you are (“Registration Information”).

**Profile Information:** For some Sogame Websites or Services, you may also have the option of providing additional information about yourself to create a user profile (“Profile”) that will be publically viewable by others. We will collect the information you share with us in creating your Profile such as your, first and last name, user name, date of birth and gender, You should exercise care and caution in creating your Profile as your Profile, including your Profile Information, will be publically viewable to others and may in some instances be index by search engines and viewable outside of the Sogame Websites and/or Services. Your Profile and/or Profile Information may be used by third parties to make contact with you in unwanted ways, and Sogame is not responsible for information you supply in your Profile and/or the manner in which it is used by others.

**Public Posting/Shared Content:** Some of the Sogame Websites or Services may allow you to interact with other users and/or post, share, communicate with, or otherwise transmit content publicly, such as by participating in player forums, message boards, news feeds, status updates, posting public comments to users’ profiles, sending messages or invitations to other users, chatting with other users, posting photo, and/or posting comments to a wall (collectively “Shared Content” or “Public Posting”). We may collect and store archives of such Public Postings on Sogame servers, and all Public Postings are subject to this Privacy Policy and may be used or disclosed pursuant to the terms of this Policy and the Terms of Service, including but not limited to protecting the safety and well being of members of the public, minors, Sogame users, our employees, and our Websites or Services.

Keep in mind that your Public Posting will be visible to anyone who has access to the Websites or Services and may in some instances be viewable outside of Sogame as such Public Postings may, in certain instances, show up in Internet searches and/or be indexed by search engines. Using certain tools, it may be possible for you or third parties to copy, cut, and/or post your Public Posting or other information to different locations (including to websites not owned/operated by Sogame). This may result in the disclosure of private information on third party websites—for which Sogame is not responsible—and, in some cases, may subject you to liability for information posted by or about you. Therefore, you should exercise caution in all Public Postings, and we recommend you do not provide personal information that may be used to identify and/or contact you in a Pubic Posting. To request removal of your personal information from our public forums, contact us at Sogame. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

On some Sogame Websites and Services, your User Name as well as your Profile Information may be displayed in conjunction with your Public Posting. Thus, those accessing this information may be able to identify you, using other available source of information, such as your related Third Party Platform account or information on other websites.

**Payment Information:** If you purchase any products or services through our Websites or Services, such as in game virtual currency or goods, we may collect certain information regarding your purchase (such as your name, zip code, purchase) as necessary to process your order, and you will be required to provide certain payment and billing information directly to our payment processing partners, such as but not limited to your name, credit card information, billing address, and zip code. We do not directly access, store or collect your credit card information, and we will not use your payment information we collect except as needed to fulfill your purchase and/or communicate with you regarding your transaction.

**Friend’s Contact Information:** If you wish to use our service to tell a friend about the Websites or Services, we may ask for your friend’s name, e-mail address and other information, (all of which we will collect and store), and we will automatically send your friend an e-mail, and one reminder, inviting him or her to use our Websites or Services. Sogame may use and store such information for several purposes including, sending e-mails to your friend and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may unsubscribe from such messages by using the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the communication. If your friend would like to request that we no longer use or store this information they may contact us at Sogame.  We may also offer you the ability to import or upload your address book contacts or enter your contact’s e-mail addresses (collectively, “Contact Information”) so that we may invite your contacts to use our Websites and Services and/or so that you may find and interact with them on our Websites and/or Services. If you provide us with your Contact Information, we will store it unless you instruct otherwise by submitting a request www.Sogame.com and we will use this information to help you and your contacts connect on our Websites and Services. All Contact Information that you provide will be subject to and governed by this Privacy Policy.

**Communications, Support Requests, Potential Abuse:** If you contact us for assistance or to report a problem, concern, potential abuse or other issue regarding the Websites, Services or a user, we may collect and store your contact information, communication, and/or other information about you, including but not limited to your name, e-mail address, User Name, ID number, location, game play or activity, and we reserve the right to conduct further research and obtain further information as necessary. We will use the information to respond to you, research your request/communication, and in accordance with provisions of this Policy.

**Sweepstakes, Promotions, and Surveys:** From time to time, we may ask you to complete a survey, participate in our loyalty programs and/or offer you the opportunity to participate in Promotions (as defined in the Terms of Service https://www. sogame.com) on our Websites, via the Services, or through a Third Party Platform. If you choose to participate in a Promotion, we will collect and store the information you provide in connection with your participation in the Promotion, such as your name, ID number, e-mail address, date of birth, phone number and whatever other information you provide, and we will use and/or disclose that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless stated otherwise, such as in the official rules (or other guidelines) of the Promotion or as stated in another privacy policy that may govern the Promotion. All of our Promotions are intended for people who are the age of majority in their respective state, province, or country unless otherwise expressly stated. In all cases where required, Promotions will have official rules or guidelines that outline what information is being collected or users will be directed to the most recent version of this Policy. In some cases, the information collected will be used only to administer the Promotion; in other cases, the information collected will be used for Sogame’s or sponsor’s marketing purposes. Your information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes and/or in accordance with this Policy. Your entry in the Promotion may also result in your being added to our mailing lists as well as those of our promotional partners associated with the contest or sweepstakes. Acceptance of a prize may require you (unless prohibited by law) to allow us to post publicly some of your information on our Website, such as on a winner’s page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. In some instances, a third-party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a Promotion on our through our Website or Service, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the sponsor or operator of the Promotion, we have no control over the information collected and you should review the official rules as well as the advertiser’s or sponsor’s privacy policy applicable to the Promotion before participating.

**Information Sharing**

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders or processing payment, that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information unless you have "opted-in" to such sharing. If you have previously opted-in to such sharing under a prior privacy policy version, you are still considered to have opted-in under this privacy policy. As stated, and whether or not you have opted-in, we may use third parties to accept and process orders for merchandise and products, including software, and such third parties may get access to your personal information for the purposes of providing services or products to you on our behalf. In addition, if you opt-out, we may share that information with third parties who send e-mails on our behalf so that they do not e-mail you.

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety.

We may request demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income) from time to time. We will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection or we have your permission. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.

In the event that we acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.
